https://webdrive.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content443.603.0290 | 866.861.9483 Privacy PolicyWebDrive Privacy PolicySouth River Technologies is committed to protecting the privacy of its customers and all those who download and/or sample our various offerings. This Privacy Policy describes how South River Technologies and it's affiliates ("WebDrive", "we", "our", or "us") collect, use and share information in connection with use of the WebDrive application and this website.We will occasionally notify our customers of new releases of the product they purchased, special upgrade pricing, and new beta availability based on the e-mail addresses in our customer database. These notices keep our customers updated on the latest release of the software.Information We CollectActivation / Registration. When you activate WebDrive we will ask for your registration code to verify license entitlement.Payment Information. When you purchase a license to the software in our online shopping cart your financial information is directed to our third-party payment processor.  We do not store your financial information/credit card information in our systems.  After purchasing through the online shopping cart our third-party payment processor will send us your name, email address, and phone number.This website uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies. Cookies are small data files that are served by our platform and stored on your device. Our site uses cookies dropped by us or hird parties for a variety of purposes including to operate and personalize the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads served by us or on our behalf by clicking on the blue icon in the corner of the ads we serve or by clicking here. Please note that, if you delete your cookies or upgrade your browser after having opted out, you will need to opt out again. Further, if you use multiple browsers or devices you will need to execute this opt out on each browser or device.How do we use the Information we collect ?We will use contact information to notify you of your registration code, purchase receipts, software update notifications.  We may occasionally send out promotional emails that contain an opt-out links to be removed from promotional emails.We will validate your registration code to ensure the license is valid.What information don't we collect ?We will not collect any usernames, passwords, url's or drive configuration information in our Software nor is this information ever transmitted to WebDrive or South River Technologies.We will not collect any file information or data accessed by WebDrive on your behalf when communicating to your configured servers, GoogleDrive service or any other online services nor is this data ever transmitted to WebDrive or South River Technologies.What information do we share ?We will not disclose your email address or any other personal or electronic information to anyone unless we reasonably believe it is necessary to comply with a subpoena, court order, law, or regulation we may disclose your personal information or file data to the extent required to fulfill our legal obligation.SecurityAll personal information is collected via secure communication (https) and is kept in a secure database that is not subject to unauthorized usage.Contact UsIf you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us at sales@webdrive.com Site Map
HomeDownloadPurchaseSupportContact UsBlog Legal
License AgreementsPrivacy PolicyMaintenance and Support PolicyCopyright and Trademark Resources
Product SheetsUse CasesVideo TutorialsAdvanced Features Resellers
Find a ResellerBecome a ResellerWant to try WebDrive?
DOWNLOAD Ready to purchase?
BUY NOW! Have a question?
CONTACT US ©2020 South River Technologies Facebook
Twitter
Google
Linkedin
